■
字幕来源：TLF
后期：TungNg
我不感到羞愧  我懂得爱
I'm not ashamed. I've known love.
我懂得拒绝
I've known rejection.
我也不怕坦白我的感受
I'm not afraid to declare my feelings.
举例来说  信任  或者友谊
Take trust, for instance, or friendship.
这些都是生命中最重要的
These are the important things in life.
它们对你有很大的帮助
These are the things that matter, that help you on your way.
如果你无法相信你的朋友们
If you can't trust your friends,
那怎么办  怎么办
well what then? What then?
这个故事可能发生在任何城市
This could have been any city.
都一样
They're all the same.
你好我是来看房子的
Hello. I've come about the room.
他叫什么名字  -我不知道
So what's his name? -I don't know.
好象叫坎贝尔还是什么的
Campbell or something.
-卡梅伦  -卡梅伦  真的
-Cameron. -Cameron? Really?
是的
That's right.
什么
What?
-你还好吗  -我很好  谢谢
-Are you comfortable? -Yes, thanks.
-你已经看过那个公寓了  -是的
-Have you seen the flat? -Yes.
-你喜欢吗  -是的  很棒
-And you like it? -Yes, it's great.
我们都喜欢  那个房间很好
We all like it. The room's nice, too,
你不觉得吗
don't you think?
宽敞  明亮  诸如此类  真他妈的好
Spacious, bright, all that sort of stuff, all that sort of crap.
是啊
Well, yes.
那我想知道一件事  到底为什么使你认为
So tell me, cos I'd like to know, what on earth could make you think...
我们想和你分享如此好的公寓呢
we'd want to share this flat with someone like you?
我对你的第一印象很糟
My first impression is that
在你身上找不到
you have none of
一个好室友的优良品质
the qualities we seek from a flatmate.
比如说举止  魅力  品味  吸引力等等
I'm talking about things like presence, charisma, style and charm.
我并不认为我们的要求很过份或者苟刻
I don't think we're asking too much, or being unreasonable.
大卫住进这里  因为他很卖力
Take David here. An accountant he may be,
虽然他也许只是个会计
but at least he tries hard.
问题是  我看不出来  你有多么努力
Trouble is, I just don't think you're trying.
嘿  卡梅伦  说真的  祝你好运
Hey, Cameron, I mean this. Good luck.
-问几个问题  -你的兴趣是什么
-Just a few questions. -What about your hobbies?
-你为什么希望住这里  -你抽烟吗
-Why do you want a room here? -Do you smoke?
当你供奉一只羊  并把它的心取出来时
When you sacrifice a goat and rip its heart out,
你会召唤地狱之火吗
do you summon hellfire?
这是个很直接的问题  你离婚了没有
It's a straightforward question. Either you're divorced or you're not.
或者  你刚刚叫了比萨
Or do you just send out for a pizza?
你偶尔吸一点点可卡因吗
Do a little freebase, maybe?
你选的黑衣服一般黑到什么程度
How do you decide which shade of black to wear?
我会播放几秒钟这盘磁带上的音乐
OK, I'm going to play you just a few seconds of this tape.
说出歌名  和主唱
Name the song, the lead singer...
以及后来他和他的乐队
and three hit singles subsequently recorded
推出的三首单曲
by him with another band.
直截了当的说吧  你所谓没有的这段情
Let me get this straight. This affair that you're "not" having...
是和一个男人还是一个女人
is it not with a man or not with a woman?
回到共同资金的问题上
Turning very briefly to corporate financing...
不  这点很重要
No, this is important.
杠杆收购是好事还是坏事
Leveraged buyouts: A good or a bad thing?
最后一个和你说这些话的人是谁
When did anyone last say to you these exact words:
你是我生命中的阳光
"You are the sunshine of my life"?
如果我告诉你我是个反基督者
And how would you react, then,
你有何反应
if I told you I was the Antichrist?
你喜欢我的照片吗
Do you like my picture?
打败他  打败他  打败他
Defeat. Defeat. Defeat.
体育爱好  私人状况  经济情况
Sporting, personal, financial,
职业  性别  所有的一切
professional, sexual and everything.
下一个
Next.
-你知道  -亚历克斯  发球
-Did you know that...? -Alex. Just serve.
我并不是想获胜
Anyway, I wasn't tryin' to win.
我只是不想贬低你的胜利  朱丽叶
I don't want to devalue your victory, Juliet.
-我没有想胜过你  -胜利和失败是一样的
-I wasn't tryin' to win. -Victory's the same as defeat.
它是对破坏本能的屈服
It's giving in to destructive urges.
你是不是从心理治疗小组那里学到的
Did you learn that in your psychotherapy group?
-讨论小组  -我还以为你早就不去了
-Discussion group. -I thought you'd stopped going.
他有太多的欲望了
He had too many of those urges.
你们这些人都应该知道这一点
You of all people should know about that.
天啊  你们两个很敏感呢
God, you two are sensitive.
我现在只不过是在暗示
All I'm doing is implying
某种丑陋  肮脏  性的交易
some kind of ugly, sordid, sexual liaison.
-我应该为此而骄傲  -你也许也应该参加
-I'd be proud of that. -Maybe you should go.
说不定你会遇见一个不错的
You'll meet someone wonderful.
找个一生相伴的人
For my life?
就在这么一个讨论小组是
A discussion group?
-我看不可能  -找个人住这个公寓
-I think not. -For the flat.
不  恐怕会找个和他一样的人
No, it'd be someone
他那样的  一个就够了  拜托你了
like him, and one's enough, thank you very much.
那个女孩呢  你的那个朋友
What about that girl? That friend of yours,
来过的那个  我喜欢她
the one that came round. I liked her.
我们似乎有点感觉
We had something.
她本可以搬进来住啊  我们很投缘
She could have moved in. We had chemistry.
-她恨你  -那她有问题
-She hated you... -She had problems.
你比她所遇见过的任何人都更恨
More than anyone she had ever met in her entire life.
就象他们说的那样
Like they say, you know,
她曾经希望改变  可是有吗
she's got to want to change, hasn't she?
-你一定就是雨果  -你一定就是朱丽叶
-You must be Hugo. -And you must be Juliet.
-请进  -多谢
-Would you like to come in? -I'd be delighted.
-你做什么工作  -我离开过一段时间
-What do you do? -I've been away for a while.
去旅行  现在我在写一本小说
Travelling. And now I'm writing a novel.
-关于什么  -关于一个牧师之死的故事
-What's it about? -It's actually about a priest who dies.
了解
I see.
也许你是对的  也许我是应该改变一下
Maybe you're right. Maybe I ought to change it.
你是对的
You're right.
我是指  有谁愿意
I mean, who wants to
读一本关于死牧师的故事呢
read another story about a dead priest?
实际上  那是关于另一个男人
In fact, it's about another guy,
他不是牧师  而且活着
he's not a priest, and he lives.
他没有死  看到了没  这样好多了
He doesn't die. See? It's better already.
写作好象很容易啊
Writing seems easy.
易如反掌  没问题
It's a breeze. No problem.
你可以接一下吗
Do you think you could answer that?
什么  电话
What, the telephone?
但是如果是我的  就说我不在
But... if it's for me, I'm not here.
好的  你不在
Right. You're not here.
好
OK.
你好
Hello?
是  对  是
Yes, it is, yes.
请问你是哪位
Who's calling, please?
对不起  但她不
Well, I'm sorry, but she's not...
她现在不在这里
she's not in right now.
不  我一点也不知道
No, I've got absolutely no idea.
你愿意留个口信吗
Would you like to leave a message?
好的  再见
OK. Goodbye.
这是个  嗯  叫布赖恩的男的
That was a guy called Brian.
-他是不是听起来很紧张  -有一点  对
-Did he sound upset? -A little bit, yeah.
-是好还是不好  -有进步
-Is that good or bad? -It's an improvement.
我是不是该接电话
Shall I get the phone?
随它去  他知道我可能在家
Just leave it. He knows I'm probably at home.
我这周上夜班
I'm working nights this week.
-你上夜班  -我是个医生
-You're working nights? -I'm a doctor.
-他是个病人  -不是  但他需要治疗
-And he's a patient? -No, but he needs treatment.
-治疗什么  -某种衰弱症
-For what? -A certain weakness.
-人类生存条件  -哦  你对那个很了解
-The human condition. -Oh. You know about it.
-我写过关于它的东西  -不是一样吗
-Well, I write about it. -And that's not the same thing?
不一样  我喜欢小说家
No. I'm like all novelists
因为他们总是探索自我
on a search of the self.
他是不是累的倒在冰箱后面了
Has he tried down the back of the fridge?
他好象不错  亚历克斯
He seemed like a nice guy, Alex.
我又没说他不是
I'm not saying he didn't seem like a nice guy.
我只是觉得有点怪异  所谓探索自我什么的
I just said it's a bit strange, this search of the self or whatever.
他并不怪啊  亚历克斯
He didn't seem strange, Alex.
他好象就是
He seemed... you know...
-有意思  -有意思
-Interesting. -Interesting?
有意思
Interesting.
你好  不  她不在
Hello? No, she's not in.
我不知道  不清楚
I don't know. I've no idea.
-是谁  -不知道  听上去象是瑞典口音
-Who was it? -I don't know. He sounded Swedish.
-你认识什么瑞典人吗  -不认识
-Do you know any Swedish men? -No.
也许只是感觉吧
Maybe it was just the emotion.
-你觉得呢  -觉得什么
-What do you think? -About what?
-关于那个雨果的人  -我没时间
-About this Hugo person. -I don't have the time.
我只是问  你感觉如何
I'm just asking what you think.
我不在乎  到目前为止
I don't care, so long as
他还不象是个怪人
he's not a freak.
大卫  这是你妈妈的笔迹  我没有打开过
David. It's your mother's handwriting. I didn't open it.
我可不想听到你爸爸便秘的事
I don't like reading about your father's constipation.
-我们会和他会面  然后呢  -什么
-So we'll meet him, then? -What?
好吧  随便  我跟你说
Yeah, yeah, whatever. I tell you,
这个家伙写的每一封信都是一样的
every letter this guy writes you is the same.
开始写的都很纯情  接着就变成色情文学了
They all begin like true love and descend into open pornography.
我梦见你的大腿
"I dream of your thighs,
触摸你白皙的肌肤令我浮想连篇
the touch of your white skin leading me in desire...
当我  勃起的  红肿的
while I, aroused and inflamed..."
勃起的  红肿的
Aroused and inflamed?
他甚至用自己的真名署名
He even signs them in his own name.
我宁可用其它人的名字
I'd sign someone else's.
比如用他的名字
I'd sign his name.
要是我写的话  不过我可不会写
If I wrote them, that is, which I don't.
有意思  她是这么描述你的
Interesting. That's what she said.
有意思  你看  这就是为什么你会在这儿
Interesting. You see, that's why you're here.
通常我不会和一般人会面
I don't usually meet people,
除非和我认识的人
unless I already know them.
-知道了  -有时  人类很残酷
-I see. -People can be so cruel.
那  嗯
So...
我们认为很好
well, we think it's fine.
啊  那么我可以住进这个房间了
So, I can have the room?
是的  你可以住进来
Yes, you can have the room.
我并不经常喝醉酒的
I'm not usually drunk.
-没有这么醉  -谈谈费用
-Not usually this drunk. -Only on expenses.
他要告诉你  他本来可以出名的
He's going to tell you he could have been someone.
而不象现在这样  但我们喜欢现在的他
Instead of what he is, which is the man we know and love.
-疲倦  空虚  -理解与爱
Tired out, empty shell of a... Know and love?
-我觉得你在说谎  -你说的对
-I think you're lying. -You're right.
你看见了  他们并不真正了解我
You see? They don't really know me.
不  亚历克斯  我们并不真正爱你
No, Alex. We don't really love you.
你可以付的起这个房间的价格吗
Can you afford this place?
哦  当然可以
Oh, yeah.
-我可以问你一个问题吗  -当然可以
-Can I ask you a question? -Certainly.
你曾杀过人吗
Have you ever killed a man?
没有
No.
那就好
That's fair enough, then.
它闻起来
Well, it certainly smells
象真的
like the real thing.
罗杰斯队在这个赛季有了一些起色
Rangers have made a few dramatic comebacks this season.
但他们不得不
But they'll really have to
全力以赴
draw on all of their resources.
-你有没有见到雨果  -没有
-Have you seen Hugo? -No.
你知道他在哪个频道里吗
Any idea which channel he's on?
爱丁堡的最高法院
The High Court in Edinburgh.
去你妈的
Oh, for fuck's sake.
不  她不在
No, she's not in.
-你有没有见过他  -我没有时间了
-Have you seen him? -I don't have the time.
-是或否  大卫  是或  -否
-Yes or no? David, yes or...? -No!
-大卫也没有见过他  -我也是这么想的
-David hasn't seen him either. -So I gathered.
-也许他不喜欢我们  -大卫
-Maybe he didn't like us. -David?
-不  雨果  -他的车还在那儿
-No, Hugo. -His car's still there.
-他有车  -是的  有什么问题
-He's got a car? -Yeah. What's wrong with that?
什么样的车
What sort of car?
我不知道  亚历克斯  我是个女孩啊
I don't know, Alex. I'm just a girl.
我再问你一次  什么样的车
I'll ask you once more. What sort of car?
蓝色的  好了吧  它还在那儿呢
A blue one, OK? And it's still there.
雨果  很抱歉  你可以开开门吗
Hugo, I'm sorry about this, but can you open your door?
是我们  你的室友
It's us, your flatmates and companions,
你的新朋友们
your new-found friends.
他不在  我一点也看不见他
He's not there. I can't see him at all.
也许他躲在衣柜里
Maybe he's in the wardrobe.
他当然不会在该死的衣柜里
Of course he's not in the bloody wardrobe.
不过是个笑话  亚历克斯
It's a joke, Alex.
我想他大概离开了
I think he probably left.
我们大概再也见不到他了
We'll probably never see him again.
亚历克斯  钥匙在另一头
Alex, the key is on the other side.
-如何  -打开它
-So? -Open it.
你要我踢开它  现在
You want me to kick this in? Now?
-是的  -好  没问题
-Yeah. -OK, no problem.
你想来一下吗
Do you want a go?
好  你估计一下
OK, you size that up.
-人死了是不是都这个样子  -是
-Is this what they always look like? -Yes.
-我在想他是怎么做的  -做什么
-Wonder how he did it. -Did what?
自杀
Killed himself.
我想是这样的
I presume that's what's happened.
你认为呢
What do you think?
-亚历克斯  -什么  有什么问题
-Alex! -What? What's wrong?
-你在干什么  -看
-What are you doing? -Looking.
-不要  -不要看
-Don't. -Don't look?
-不  -为什么不
-No. -Why not?
有什么问题  你就不怀疑他是怎么死的
What's wrong? Don't you wonder what he died from?
不  那家伙已经死了  你还想要什么
No. The guy's dead. What more do you need?
这可不是每天发生在我公寓的故事
It's not every day I find a story in my own flat.
这不是个故事  亚历克斯  这是个死尸
It's not a story, Alex, it's a corpse.
我从来没见过死人
I've never seen a dead body before.
当然我见过我的祖母  不过我想那不算数
I saw my grandmother, of course, but I don't suppose that counts.
她那时还活着
She was alive at the time.
你能过来看一样东西吗
Can I show you something?
紧急呼叫中心  需要什么服务
Emergency. Which service?
紧急呼叫中心  需要什么
Emergency. Which...?
-不  -想想而已
-No. -Just think about it.
-不  -拜托  大卫
-No. -Come on, David.
-不  -朱丽叶
-No. -Juliet?
-不  亚历克斯  它  -它什么
-No, Alex. It's... -It's what?
-不可能的  -就这些
-Unfeasible. -Is that all?
-你的意思是不道德  -我知道我在说什么
-You mean immoral. -I know what I mean.
我只是请你想象一下
I'm only asking you to think about it.
这是邪恶的想法  亚历克斯  这不好
It's a sick idea, Alex. It's sick.
别告诉我  你一点都不动心
But don't tell me you're not tempted.
别告诉我  你一点都不感兴趣
Don't tell me you're not interested.
-我太了解你了  -你这么认为
-I know you well enough. -You think so?
去吧  那你去打电话吧
Go ahead, then. Telephone.
打给警察
Telephone the police.
去吧  没人会阻止你
Go ahead. No one's gonna stand in your way.
打电话给他们  告诉他们
Telephone them. Tell them.
告诉他们有一个手提箱里装满了钱
Tell them there's a suitcase full of money,
而且你不想要
and you don't want it.
房间里是不是有宠物  是的  有一个
Was there a pet in the house? Yeah, a pet.
比如狗  鹦鹉  沙鼠  或什么
You know, like a dog or a budgie or a gerbil or something?
我需要的是电脑把小老鼠
What I need here is "PC Plod saves Harry the Hamster
从恐怖屋拯救出来
from house of horror".
好的  可惜  你看  没有宠物
All right. Well, that's a pity. You see, no pets
没有人间角落
no human angle.
喂  你  那个家伙怎么了
Hi, there. What happened to that guy?
那个家伙
What guy?
那个死掉的家伙
That guy. The one that died.
-死掉的  -上个礼拜死掉的那个
-Died? -That one last week.
-这里  -是  这里  还有哪里
-Here? -Yes, here. Where else?
哦  他啊  他死了
Oh, him. Well, he died.
我也是这么想的
That's what I thought.
你好  你有没有放小行李的房间
Hello? Have you got room for an overnighter?
他还在这儿
He's still here?
是的  因为他没办法发动他的车
Yeah, he couldn't get his car started.
你什么时候告诉警察
When are you gonna let the police know?
随时都可以啊  只要你愿意  大卫
You phone them if you want, David.
那你呢
What about you?
我已经习惯他在周围了
I'm getting used to having him around.
我们在这儿做什么  大卫
What is it we do here, David?
-什么  -这儿
-Sorry? -Here.
-这儿  -这个公司
-Right here? -In this firm.
-这个问题范围很广  -会计学  大卫
-Well, it's a wide range of... -Accounting, David.
特许会计是受人嘲笑的  你意识到了吗
Chartered accounting is of ten sneered at. Were you aware of that?
并不是所有的都象它一样受人嘲笑
Not any real sneering as such, no.
外面的世界很大
There's a whole wide world out there...
所有的都需要会计去计算  不是吗
and it all needs to be accounted for, does it not?
-我  -他们爱嘲笑  不是吗
-Well, I... -They sneer, do they not?
-我不敢肯定  -它不流行
-I'm not sure. -It's unfashionable.
不过是的  我们有条不紊
But yes, we're methodical, yes,
我们努力  认真
we're diligent, yes, we're serious.
那里面发生了什么问题呢
And where's the crime in that?
为什么不在屋顶喊叫呢
Why not shout it from the rooftops?
也许我们有点令人讨厌
Maybe sometimes we're a wee bit boring,
但是  我们把工作完成了
but, by God, we get the job done.
是的  先生
Yes, sir.
那就是我认为你合适留在这里的原因
That's why I think you fit in here.
-我很无趣  -但你可以把工作完成的很好
-I'm boring? -You get the job done.
我知道了  我以为你是指
I see. I thought you meant...
这就是为什么我放心的让你去接这个客户
Which is why I trust you with this client.
早上好  有什么可以帮忙的吗
Good morning. Can I help you?
是的  我帮你看一下
Yeah, I'll just check that for you.
干吧
Let's do it.
我们先谈谈怎么处理
Let's talk about disposal.
我们必须令尸体无法分辨
We have to make that body unidentifiable.
火烧  扔进海里  掩埋都有问题
Burning, dumping at sea and burial are all flawed...
据我所知  都可以查到指纹或牙齿档案
either by fingerprints or more commonly by dental records, I have learnt.
我建议  把他埋到树林里
What I suggest is that we bury him out in the forest.
首先  我们把他的手和脚卸下来  烧掉
First we remove his hands and his feet, which we incinerate.
还有他的牙齿  只要除掉就行
And his teeth, which we just remove.
和那些活一样简单
It's as simple as that.
大卫
David.
我一直在想这些都是派什么用的  现在
I've always wondered what these were for. Now...
这是我们要的
This is what we need.
而且  嗯
And...
这个
This.
-还要什么  -我不知道
-What else? -I don't know.
一个铁锹  我们需要一个铁锹
A spade. We need a spade.
我希望你精神集中一点
I wish you'd concentrate.
我们需要一个铁锹挖一个坑
We need a spade to dig a pit.
-谁会去做  -挖坑
-Who's gonna do it? -Dig the pit?
-不是那个  -谁做什么
-Not that. -Who's gonna do what?
你知道我在说什么
You know what I'm talking about.
是吗  你在说什么
Do I? What are you talking about?
你知道的  谁会去做
You know what. Who's gonna do it?
我们一起  大卫
We all are, David.
我们一起做
We're all gonna do it.
你  我  还有朱丽叶
You, me and Juliet
每个人都有份
will do his or her bit.
公平吗
Fair enough?
-我做不了  -我听不见
-I can't do it. -I don't hear this.
-我没办法做  -你已经打算退出了
-I won't be able to do it. -You want out already?
你不想得到那些钱
You don't want the money?
雨果已经开始腐烂了  他已经发臭了
Hugo is going off! He smells!
公寓也臭了我们不能再等了
The flat smells! We can't wait!
我没办法把他分尸
I won't be able to cut him up.
-谁会去做  -我认为我们应该一起做
-Who's going to do it? -I thought we all were.
我觉得我做不到
I don't think I can.
但是  朱丽叶  你是个医生
But, Juliet, you're a doctor.
你每天都在杀人
You kill people every day.
不一样的  我还是不想做
That's different. I still don't want to.
你现在才告诉我这个
Now you tell me.
有件事我想问
There's something I want to ask.
我不知道我向上帝发誓  我不知道
I don't know! I swear to God, I don't know!
家人  朋友
Family? Friends?
抓起来  想想看
Drugged-up, wandering,
自杀的那些杂种没有家人
suicidal fuck-ups don't have families.
我本以为我们可以讨论一下
I just thought we should discuss it.
拿起他的腿
Take his legs.
雨果在哪里
Where's Hugo?
-把他提起来  -嘘
Pick him up.
我向上帝发誓  我不知道  我不知道
I swear to God, I don't know! I don't know!
愚蠢的狗杂种
Stupid fuckin' bastard.
要不然我们抽签决定
Why don't we draw lots for it?
谁抽到短的  就让他一个人干
Whoever draws the short straw does it all.
这样  你要么别干  要么就干完
That way you either do it or you don't.
-好  我可以  -大卫
-OK. I can go with that. -David?
-我不知道  -如果我抽到短的  我来做
-I don't know. -If I draw the short straw, I'll do it.
但如果你不肯干
But I'm not gonna do it
我是绝对不会干的
just because you won't.
好吧  就这么说定了
All right, then. Here we are and this is it.
你到底参加不参加
Do you wanna play or not?
我做不了
I can't do it.
-完成了  -好  但还没完全结束
-Finished. -All right, but not quite.
-深度够吗  -别担心
-Is that going to be deep enough? -Don't worry.
有必要吗
Is this necessary?
是的  别废话了  要么别做  要么做完
Yes. Now come on. All or nothin'.
你还好吧
Are you all right?
哦  是的  我很好  谢谢  很好
Oh, yes. I'm fine, thanks. Just fine.
-你想说出来吗  -不
-Would you like to talk about it? -No.
这三个人都有机会
These three people get their chance to...
失去一百万
lose a million.
是的  大家好
Yes, all right. Hello there
欢迎来到我们的百万游艇节目
and welcome aboard our millionaire's yacht.
就好象是玛丽·斯莱斯特
It's just like the "Marie Celeste"
只不过缺少了派对气氛
but without the party atmosphere.
正如你们所知
As you know,
我们节目的目标不是赢  而是
the object is not to win the game, but to...
输
Lose.
不是给出正确的答案  而是
Not to give right answers, but...
错误的答案
Wrong ones.
不是要做的好  而是要做的
Not to do well, but to do really...
糟糕
Badly.
最重要的是努力
And above all to try
做成一个大杂烩
and make a total... hotchpotch.
小心了
Be careful.
亚历克斯!
Alex!
我不明白为什么不能藏在下面
I don't know why we couldn't stuff it under the floorboards.
不要罗嗦  亚历克斯
Stop nagging, Alex.
我们原本可以把它藏在冰箱里
We could have hid it in the fridge.
先生们  女士们
Ladies and gentlemen,
请注意了
could I have your attention, please?
感谢大家今天来到这里
I'd like to thank you all for coming tonight...
帮助我们为疾病儿童基金会
to help us raise funds
筹集基金
for the sick children's unit.
你从来没跟我说过这是为了儿童
You never told me this was for children.
我讨厌儿童
I hate children.
我宁可捐钱杀了那帮小王八蛋
I'd raise money to have the little fuckers put down.
把钱还给我
I want my money back!
在跳舞开始之前
But before the dancing starts...
-对不起  -我希望投票以感谢
-Excuse me! -.. I would like to give a vote of thanks...
那些为了这一切
to the few people who have worked
辛勤工作的人们
so hard to make this occasion happen.
-你认识这些人吗  -他们是我的朋友
-Do you know these people? -They're my friends.
哦  那如果他们想和你说话
Oh, so if they want to speak to you,
我们就告诉他们你不在
we tell them that you're not here?
但是先生们和女士们
But ladies and gentlemen
以及其它的
and those of you who are neither or both...
他们在哪里发现他的
Where did they dig him up?
奏一曲剥柳树叶舞曲
Form sets for "Strip the Willow".
我们跳舞去吗
Are we going to dance?
那可是肉体接触啊  不是吗
Well, it's physical contact, isn't it?
好
OK.
告诉我
Talk to me.
好
OK.
不不要请不要
No! Don't! Please don't!
不不
No! No!
求你了
Please!
我们可以谈谈吗
Can we talk about something?
现在不行  我不知道
Not now. I have an idea.
这很重要  我们需要决定
It's important. We need to decide...
你能不能不要再担心了
Will you just stop worrying?
为了爱和永远的快乐
To love and to happiness for ever.
永远永远
For ever and ever.
-怎么了  -我有话要说
-What's wrong? -I want to talk now.
除非你为了爱和永远的快乐而醉倒以后
When you've drunk to love and happiness.
-现在  -以后
-Now. -After.
大卫  我保证我们会让他一直快乐
David, I promise we will. Just keep him happy.
不是为了我
It's not for me.
是为了爱和永远的快乐
It's for love and happiness for ever.
看那边  是卡梅伦
Look over there. It's Cameron.
-谁  -你记得卡梅伦吗
-Who? -You remember Cameron.
-不  -他在这儿干什么
-No. -What's he doing here?
-不是他  -就是他  卡梅伦
-That's not him. -It is. Cameron!
卡梅伦  过来  过来
Cameron, come on over here. Come on.
什么
What?
没什么  我们以为你是另一个人
Nothing. We thought you were someone else.
祝你好运
Good luck!
-他为什么老跟着我们  -我想说的是这个
-Why does he have to follow us around? -What I was wanting to say was this.
-可爱的朱丽叶  好久不见了  -布赖恩
-The divine Juliet. Long time no see. -Brian.
你可以和我跳一支舞吗
Would you care to dance?
等一下  你以为你是什么人
Hold on. Who do you think you are?
-什么  -你以为你是什么人
-What? -Who do you think you are?
你打断我们的对话
You interrupted us.
我是布赖恩·麦金利  你是谁
I'm Brian Mckinley. And who are you?
好  布赖恩·麦金利
Well, Brian Mckinley,
你要是想  和我的女朋友跳舞
if you wanna talk to my girlfriend,
先要过我这一关
you talk to me first.
你要是想跳舞  先提前三周申请
If you wanna dance, you apply three weeks in advance...
要不然  你会死在他妈的垃圾袋里
or you're gonna end up inside a fucking bin bag!
你没有申请  所以别想跳舞
You didn't apply, so you don't dance.
你觉得下次你会更暴力吗
Do you think you could be a little more forceful next time?
对不起
I'm sorry.
不  不  我想他已经领会了
No, no. I think he got the message.
刚才真是紧张
That was quite stressful.
是  但你刚才真棒  他真棒
Yeah, but you were good. He was really good.
他妈的垃圾袋  我爱这个词
Fuckin' bin bag, I like that.
你真是体现了你的阳刚之气
You really explored your maleness to the full there.
-真的  -你刚才做的漂亮极了
-You think so? -You certainly had a good look around.
你太棒了
You were magnificent.
是
Yeah.
他妈的垃圾袋
Fuckin' bin bag.
卡梅伦吓我一跳
Cameron! What a surprise!
你好
Hello?
-是谁  -我不知道
-Who was it? -I don't know.
-没人说过  -或者是他自己想一言不发
-No one said anything. -Or rendered speechless with desire.
我又回想起了那些日子的感觉
I recall that feeling from the days when I had such a thing.
-你还好吗  -不好
-Are you all right? -No.
那我们花点钱吧
Then let's spend some money.
你好  这段日子的确是很艰难
Hello. It's been a struggle,
但担惊受怕的日子已经结束了
but now our days of worry are over.
通道尽头的光线已经变成了金色的阳光
The light at the end of the tunnel has expanded into a golden sunrise.
在最后  漫长的最后
And now at last, at long last,
任何事情都不会再相同
nothing will ever be the same again.
这是来自亚历克斯·劳私人视频日记的报道
This is Alex Law reporting on the video diary of his own life.
我告诉你  我开心死了
Let me tell you, I'm so happy I could die.
我觉得我们应该停止了  好吗
I think we ought to stop this, don't you?
哦  你放松一下好吗
Oh, will you relax?
你让我们都很紧张
You're making us all nervous.
-你为这个花了多少钱  -我不知道
-How much did you pay for this? -I don't know.
-我不记得了  -告诉我你花了多少钱
-I can't remember. -Tell me how much you paid.
-我不记得了  -你到底花了多少钱
-I can't remember. -How much did you pay for this?
不知道  不知道
No idea. I don't know.
到底花了多少钱
How much did you pay for this?!
-500块  -500块
-500. -500?
你为了这个花了500块
You paid 500 for this?
它就是这个价格
That's what it cost.
不  是你花了这么多在这上面
No. That's what you paid for it.
你花了500块在这上面
500 is what you paid for it.
我们目前还不知道这东西的代价是什么
We don't know how much it cost us yet.
你们两个倒是逍遥
For you two to have a good time.
但代价是什么  我们并不知道
We don't know the cost of that yet.
对不起  他们拿了什么吗
Excuse me. Did they take anything?
这些够了吗
Is that enough for you?
吃的
Oi.
-什么  -这些够了没有
-What? -Is that enough for you?
-是  够了  -还有很多
-Yes, that's fine. -There's plenty more.
够了
That's fine.
-怎么了  -没什么
-What's wrong? -Nothing.
-你不吃饭  -吃什么
-You're not eating. -Eating what?
你不象以前那吃东西了
You're not eating like you used to.
你把碟子给我  我会吃的
If you give me the plate, I'll eat.
现在  给我狼吞虎咽
Now swallow.
你应该花点钱
You should spend some money
而不应该老是担心  这是我给你的建议
instead of worrying about it.
你会感觉好很多
You'd feel much better.
一旦花掉它  你就不担心了
Once it's spent, you don't have to worry.
它象是担子从身上卸掉了
It'll be a weight off your shoulders.
你明白这个道理
You know we're right.
我要把保证它的安全
I wanna secure it.
保证它的安全  你打算把它存到银行里吗
Secure it? You wanna put it in a bank?
你不会是想存到银行里吧
You don't wanna put it in a bank, do you?
你想把它埋起来
Do you want to bury it?
我不明白  这是很蠢的
I don't see the point. It's stupid.
这本来就很蠢  我们拿了这笔钱
Course it's stupid. We took the money.
这是很实际的想法
It was a material calculation.
如果这钱是在某个秘密的银行里
What's the point if it's underground in some funny bank
或其它什么地方  有什么意义呢
in some funny place?
如果你不能拥有它  挥霍它
If you can't have it, spend it,
那它还有什么用呢  什么用也没有
then what use is it? None.
所有的都白费了  我不想白费心血
It's all for nothing. I didn't get into this for nothing,
那样我就什么都没有了
so that I could have nothing.
是  你又没有看到他腿被锯断的样子
Yeah, and you didn't saw his feet off.
不一样的感觉
Tastes different.
大卫  你在上面干什么
David, what are you doin' up there?
你现在可以下来吗
Will you come down now?
上面不安全
It's not safe up there.
你听到我说的吗
Are you listening to me?
安全和疯狂不是一回事
Security and insanity are not the same thing.
妈的
Shit.
我不管  一个成人不应该住在阁楼上
I don't care. A grown man shouldn't be living in a loft.
他在上面不安全
He isn't safe up there.
如果你在乎他  你应该说服他下来
If you cared about him at all, you'd use your influence to get him down.
-那钱呢  -我们可以放到其它地方
-And the money? -We could put it somewhere.
放到他找不到的地方
Where he can't get it?
这是你的主意  不是我的
Well, you thought of that, not me.
算了  他会下来的
Forget it. He'll come down.
哦  朱丽叶  听我说
Oh, Juliet, look.
你好  朗姆斯顿先生
Hello, Mr Lumsden.
这里是大卫·史蒂文斯
It's David Stevens here.
对不起  先生  我今天去不了公司了
I'm sorry, sir. I won't be able to make it to the office today.
是我妈妈  先生  她病的很重
It's my mother, sir. She's very ill
我想  现在我应该陪在她身边
and I think I need to be with her just now.
我不知道  医生也不能肯定  都有可能
I don't know. The doctors aren't sure. It could go either way.
是的  先生  我会保持联系的
Yes, sir. I'll certainly stay in touch.
-好天  -什么
-Good day? -What?
-好天  -你在说什么
-Good day? -What are you talking about?
我只想问你今天过的好不好
I'm just asking if you had a good day.
为什么
Why?
我想我们可以谈谈
Well, I thought I'd make conversation.
请你不要这样
Please, I'd rather you didn't.
-你在等什么人吗  -没有
-Are you expecting anyone? -No.
你不打算去开门
Aren't you going to answer it?
我也没有在等什么人
Well, I'm not expecting anyone either.
在阁楼
It's in the loft!
In the loft!
9月19日  伦敦希思罗机场到里约热内卢
September 19, London Heathrow to Rio de Janeiro.
是英国航空公司  你选的是765
It's British Airways. You're looking at 765.
是7-6-5
That's 7-6-5.
听起来不错  -葡萄牙航空公司
That sounds fine. -Air Portugal,
在另一方面
on the other hand...
途经里斯本  同一天
it's via Lisbon, the same day.
是565  5-6-5
It's 565. 5-6-5.
膳食服务对你重要吗
Is catering important?
-什么  -法国航空公司  格拉斯哥直航
-What? -Air France, Glasgow direct.
那样的话  你就会看到912
But then you're looking at the wrong end of 912.
是9-1-2
That's 9-1-2.
第一个很好  伦敦希思罗机场直航
The first one was fine. Heathrow direct.
随便你
It's up to you.
巴塔哥尼亚航空公司  全新的装备
Air Patagonia, that's a new outfit.
途经途经很多地方  的确
Via... via lots of different places, really.
没有膳食服务
It's no catering.
是411  4-1-1
That's 411. 4-1-1.
非常超值  但是要在波哥大加油
It's good value, but refuelling at Bogot?...
第一个很好
The first one was fine.
随便你  7-6-5
It's up to you. 7-6-5.
你打算怎么付款
How will you be paying?
哦  天啊  哦  上帝啊
Oh, God! Oh, Jesus Christ!
哦  天啊
Oh, my God!
上帝
Christ!
不  不  上帝  不上帝
No, no. Dear God. No! Christ!
不  就这样  我拒绝再继续讨论
No, and that's it. I refuse to discuss it any further.
-这是唯一的办法  -我拒绝
-It's the only way. -I refuse.
你怕了
You're frightened.
我不怕  我只是受一点点惊吓
I'm not frightened. I'm a little terrified.
你有没有看见最后两个人是怎么样的
Did you see what happened to the last two people?
他们活着上去  死着下来
They went up alive and they came back down dead.
你看到了吗  我的意思是
Did you notice that? The difference,
不一样了  活的  死的  死的  活的
I mean. Alive, dead -dead, alive.
不难发现
It wasn't difficult to spot.
他把他们都宰了
He killed them both.
他把他们都砍死了
He cut them up.
是的  但你会好好的
Yeah, but you'll be all right.
为什么
And how's that?
因为你比他聪明
Because you're smarter than he is.
是  我也一直这么认为的
Yeah, well, that's what I've always thought.
晚上好  我是探长马克
Good evening. I'm Detective Inspector McCall.
这位是DC  米切尔
This is DC Mitchell.
我们能不能问你几个问题
I wonder if we could ask some questions.
-关于什么  -关于那起入室行窃
-What about? -It's about the burglary.
-入室行窃  -在楼下
-Burglary? -Downstairs.
-哦  是的  -我们可以进来吗
-Of course. -Can we come in?
我当时只是听到她的哭声和求救声
So I just heard her cries for help
仅此而已
and all that.
当我下楼后  那里还有很多其它的人
When I went downstairs, there were other people there.
所以我就站在那里  等着  和其它人一样
So I just stood around, you know, waiting, the way people do.
当你的同事到了之后  我就上楼了
And when your colleagues arrived, I came back upstairs.
就这些  我没有看到
That's about all, I think. I didn't actually see
任何有价值的东西  没有
anything useful, I don't think.
其它的三个人  他们有没有听到什么
And the other three people, did they hear anything?
只有其它两个人在这所公寓里
There are only two other people in the flat.
-两个  -谁说有四个人
-Two? -Who said there were four?
我们以为有四个人住在这里
We understood there were four people living here.
并不一直是  但现在是四个
Not always, but now four.
不  三个  谁告诉你们有四个人
No, three. Who said there were four?
真奇怪  这种误导信息实在令人无法满意
How strange. And how unsatisfactory to have misleading information.
这里只有三个人
Only three people here?
-你肯定  -是的  绝对肯定
-You're sure? -Yes, absolutely.
是谁说有四个
Who said there were four?
记录下来  米切尔
Make a note of that, Mitchell.
只有三个人  而不是四个  记下来
Only three rather than four. Write it down.
你可以用数字或文字  我无所谓
You can use numbers or words. I've no preference.
-你用哪一个  -全部
-Which are you using? -Both, sir.
好极了
Excellent.
DC  米切尔是个有前途的明星
DC Mitchell is a rising star,
史蒂文斯先生
Mr Stevens.
在我的监护下  他绝对会升级的
Under my tutelage, he will undoubtedly make the grade.
-了解  -我比较怀疑
-I see. -I doubt it.
-你在大厅里等  -是的
-You'll wait in the hall? -I'll wait.
如果听起来象是我被杀死了
If it sounds like I'm getting killed,
马上打电话给警察  告诉他们一切
call the police and tell them everything.
除非是他首先提出这个主意
Except maybe that it was his idea in the first place.
那很重要  我不想让他们知道
That's important.
我死的真正原因
I need to die misunderstood.
-亚历克斯  -什么
-Alex. -What?
虽然你很聪明
As smart as you are,
但还是可能需要一点帮助
you might need a little help.
大卫  我要上来
David, what I'm gonna do is
打开这个保险箱
I'm gonna open this lock and I'm gonna come up.
重要是的你要保持冷静
But what's really important is that you remain calm.
好吗
OK?
亚历克斯
Alex?
没什么  一只鸽子
It's all right. It's just a pigeon.
他不在上面
Well, he isn't up here.
叫他找钱
Tell him to look for the money.
找一下钱在哪里
Look for the money.
不要担心  我正在找
Don't worry. That's exactly what I'm doin'.
不在上面  他独吞了
It's not up here. He has eaten it.
你在找我
Are you looking for me?
对  在找你
Looking for you, yeah.
为什么  你想要什么  钱  是吗
What for? What did you want? The money? Was that it?
我们只是想和你谈谈
We just wanted to talk to you.
你还想和谁谈
Who else have you just wanted to talk to?
也许你以为他们已经盯上我了
Maybe you thought they'd already got me.
-谁  -你的朋友们
-Who? -Your friends.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talkin' about.
他不知道  大卫
He doesn't know, David.
也许他不知道
Maybe you don't.
我说的是警察
I'm talking about the police.
我以为你去上班了
I thought you'd gone to work.
带着这张脸
With a face like this?
亚历克斯  编辑要见你
Alex, the editor wants to see you.
-对不起  -你应该的
-I'm sorry. -So you should be.
也许我们还是可以把事情解决的
Maybe we can still sort everything out.
我们当然可以试试
Well, we can certainly try.
三具尸体  已经腐烂  毁容  无法辨认
Three bodies. Decomposed. Mutilated beyond recognition.
-我什么也不知道  -你当然不知道
-I don't know anythin' about it. -Of course you don't.
如果你知道什么  我就不用派你去调查了
If you knew anything about it, I wouldn't have to send you to cover it.
-调查  -对  你也可以乘机休息一下
-Cover it? -That's right. This is your break, son.
调查
Cover it?
天啊
Jesus.
好的  今天到目前为止
All right. The releasable and printworthy facts of the day
有如下几件事是值得报道的
so far are as follows.
昨天晚些时候  森林工人发现一具死尸
Late yesterday, forestry workers came across one set of human remains...
埋的地方看起来最近被挖掘过
in a grave which appeared to have been recently dug.
进一步的挖掘后
Further excavation revealed another deeper grave
又发现了另外两具尸体
with two sets of remains.
是连环杀人案吗
Is this a serial killer?
为什么他们还没有被辨认出来
How come they haven't been identified?
有没有明显的动机
Any obvious motive here?
有一个人被剥了皮是真的吗
Is it true that one has been skinned?
并不完全是这样
Not entirely.
好的  好的  有一处皮肤被剥掉了
All right, all right. An area of skin "has" been removed.
也许你们对这个感兴趣
And you'd better keep this to yourselves.
没有手  没有脚  也没有了牙齿
There's no hands, no feet, no teeth.
脸部完全无法辨认  是的
The face is totally unrecognisable and, yes...
有一具尸体的皮肤被剥掉了
skin has been removed from one of the bodies.
当尸体被清理后
As and when the corpses are removed...
我们会尽力找出杀人动机和死亡时间
we will endeavour to ascertain the mode of death and duration of burial...
以及被害人身份
as well as identification, which will of course be passed on to you...
可能的话  在通知家属以后
after informing, where possible,
这些都会告诉你们
the next of kin.
-你还好吗  -是的  当然
-Are you OK? -Yes, of course.
怎么会不好
Why wouldn't I be?
我不知道  我以为也许
I don't know. I just thought maybe...
我们刚才在研究问题
We were just sorting things out.
-你最好看一下这个  -我们已经知道了
-You'd better read all about it. -We already know.
电视里有
It was on the television.
当然  不过指纹提供了更明确的
Of course, but print provides a more lucid and...
闭嘴  亚历克斯
Oh, shut up, Alex.
不够深  我告诉过你挖的不够深
It wasn't deep enough. I told you it wasn't deep enough
你就是不听
and you wouldn't listen.
这没关系
It doesn't necessarily matter.
他们不知道那些人是谁
They don't know who they are
也没有线索关联到我们  没有
and have nothing to connect us with them. Nothing.
我真高兴你如此肯定  亚历克斯
I'm glad you're so certain, Alex.
这令我们好受多了
It makes us feel a whole lot better.
请再说一遍
I beg your pardon?
这令我们感觉好多了
It makes us feel a whole lot better.
我就知道他会这么说
That's what I thought he said.
嘘  停
Stop.
你在这儿干什么
What are you doin' here?
关于我和大卫
It's about me and David.
你们真是完美的一对啊
The perfect couple, I should say.
你不用这个样子
You mustn't take it so badly.
不要担心  换了我  我也会这么做
Don't worry. I'd do exactly the same thing,
只不过  我不是他要的类型
only I don't think I'm his type.
-你就不能住口  -不行
-Don't you ever stop? -No.
不用急  医生
Take all the time you like, Doctor.
没有  我从来没见过他们
No, I've never seen any of them.
再看看  如果你愿意的话
Look again, if you like.
对不起  我没见过他们
I'm sorry, I haven't seen them.
-你对脸的记忆力好吗  -和其它人一样
-Do you have a good memory for faces? -The same as everyone else.
但是你工作的时候
But in your work
你一定每天遇到很多人
you must meet lots of people every day.
新的人  新的面孔
New people, new faces.
是的
Yes.
你能记得他们大多数人的名字  脸吗
What do you recognise most, names or faces?
疾病
Diseases.
就象通过犯罪手法认出罪犯一样
Like recognising criminals by their crimes.
-我想是的  -我是说  就是这个样子的
-I suppose so. -I meant, that's what it's like.
-对不起  -你说你想是的
-Sorry? -You said you supposed so.
-我说这个并不是想争辩  -他不是想争辩
-I wasn't offering it for debate. -He wasn't offering it for debate.
就象根据犯罪手法认出罪犯一样
Like recognising criminals by their crimes.
没有  我从来没见过这些人
No, I've never seen any of these men before.
看看开头的两个人
Take a look at the first two.
不  我不认识他们
No, I don't know them.
如果我告诉你们
If I told you
他们的车现在就停在外面
their car was parked outside just now,
你会不会觉得奇怪
would that surprise you?
是  我想是
Yes, I suppose so.
是真的吗
Well, is it?
-什么  -停在哪里
-What? -Parked there?
不  现在不在了
No. Not any more.
我只是想  是否会令你奇怪
I just wondered if it would surprise you.
-就这样  -就这些
-That's it. -That's all?
是的
Yes.
很抱歉浪费了你的时间
Sorry to waste your time.
哦  没有  没关系
Oh, not at all. Don't worry.
-问你件事  -你的手表
-One thing. -Your watch.
-你的手表  -是真货吗
-Your watch. -Is it real?
哦  不  这是个假的
Oh, no. It's a fake.
我从泰国买的  秒针已经不会动了
I got it in Thailand. The second hand doesn't sweep.
-了解  -好
-I see. -Right.
跟你说  如果你想起这几个家伙
Tell you what. If you do remember these guys...
请打这个电话号码和我联系
maybe you could give me a phone on this number.
任何时间都可以
Any time you like.
我什么也没有告诉他们
I didn't tell them anything,
绝对没有  他们只是问问
nothing at all, absolutely nothing. They're plods.
如果他们有任何的证人
If they had any witnesses,
证据  早就说出来了
any forensic evidence, they would have whipped it out.
他们知道
They know.
他们想知道什么就能知道什么
They can know all they like.
-他们知道  -他们知道又怎样
-They know. -So? They know.
又怎样  没有任何线索可以
So what? There's nothing to
把我们和死尸联系起来
connect us with that body stuff.
除了钱
Except the money.
他是正确的  亚历克斯  他们知道
He's right, Alex. They know.
拜托接电话
Come on.
我们办公室已经关闭了
My office is closed.
但是生命仍然在前进
Life, however, grinds on towards its conclusion.
你也许想要留个口信
In the meantime, you may wish to leave a message,
但决定权是你的
but the final decision is yours.
大卫  你忘记叫我醒我了
David? You forgot to wake me.
-那我们走吧  -你和我
-So let's go. -You and me?
一起
Together.
嘿亚历克斯你这么晚
Hey! Alex!
还在打电话给谁
Who are you calling at this time of night?
到这儿来  和我们说说话
Come out here and talk to us.
是不是春宵热线啊  对吗
Well? Sex lines, is that it?
成人服务  交互性幻想
Triple-X-rated, interactive fantasies?
老毛病了  改不掉
Old habits die hard.
我刚才正在给你妈妈打电话
I was phoning your mother.
你这个老恶魔
You old devil.
好了  你已经看到  我们马上要走了
Well, anyway. As you can see, we're leaving.
我整理好东西了
So I gathered.
对不起  就是这个样子
I'm sorry, but that's the way it is.
不要担心  我会把你的邮件转发给你的
Don't worry. I'll forward your mail.
不用了
No, really.
对不起  我没有通知你
I am sorry. Sorry to be ducking out on you.
希望你不要介意
I hope you won't take it personally.
不  不  不要担心  这样大概最好了
No, no. Don't let it worry you. It's probably for the best.
这样最好
All for the best. Exactly.
我也不想看到大家沮丧
I wouldn't want things to end on a downer.
-完全没有  -我是说  人生有起有伏
-Not at all. -I mean, we've ups and downs, right.
有顺境  有逆境
Good times, bad times.
我们可以彻夜长谈
We could talk all night,
不过我们要走了  对吧
but we have to go. Don't we?
是的
Yes.
-而你也应该去睡觉了  -是的
-And you need your sleep. -Yes.
一点也不要紧
No, I can't think of anything else that matters.
-关于你的信件  -你这样很好  但是
-About your mail. -Very good of you to offer, but...
你打算去哪里
Where do you think you'll go?
我们去哪儿
Where will we go?
朱丽叶
Juliet?
-我不知道  -别害羞啊  亲爱的
-I don't know. -Don't be so coy, dear.
你要去里约热内卢啊
You're going to Rio.
-什么  -对
-What? -That's right.
里约热内卢  你一个人
Rio de Janeiro, on your own.
你应该知道
You should know.
你自己买的那该死的机票
You bought the fucking ticket!
你看见了吗
Did you see that?
我敢打赌  在她叫你上阁楼之前
I bet she didn't show you that
没让你见过这个吧  她之前说了什么
before she sent you up there. What did she say?
我们把钱分掉  一人一半
We'll split it together, you and me, fifty-fifty.
但我敢打赌  你没有说过要分给他一份
But I bet you didn't say you'd split on him.
不是这样的
It wasn't like that.
不要骗我  不要对我这样
Don't lie to me. Don't treat me like that.
我买的
I bought it.
什么
What?
我买的机票  她的和我的  是我的主意
I bought the tickets. For her and for me. It was my idea.
你的主意  我知道了
Your idea. I see.
那就对了
Well, that fits.
我是说  你和她很相衬
I mean, you and him fit together.
我早就应该看出来的
I should have seen that a long time ago.
亚历克斯  阻止他
Alex, stop him!
不  让他走  让他带着所有的钱走
No, let him go. Let him have it all.
朱丽叶  让他走
Juliet, let him go.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
你不应该打她
You shouldn't have hit her!
你想怎么样都行  但不可以打她
Do what you like, but you shouldn't have hit her!
你想要
You want it?
啊哈!
Aagh!
你这个混蛋
You bastard!
你做的对
You did the right thing.
但我不能带你走
But I can't take you with me.
保重  妈啊
Be OK, Mummy.
哦  我会很好的
Oh, I'll be all right.
你好  探长
Hello, Inspector.
哦  是的  我相信朋友
Oh, yes. I believe in friends.
我相信我们需要朋友
I believe we need them.
但是如果有一天
But, if one day
你发现你再也无法相信他们
you find that you just can't trust them any more...
那怎么办
well what then?
怎么办
What then?